Finding aid for the Sylvia Plath collection MRBC.MS.00045
Mortimer Rare Book Collection
- Writings, 1949-1963; 1; 9.3 linear feet (17 boxes; 8 oversize folders)
  - Poetry, approximately 1950-2008; 5; 7.2 linear feet (12 boxes; 8 oversize folders)
    - Photocopy of a typescript of the last 8 stanzas of "Full Fathom Five" (Box 9, Folder 102, Item 2)
      Photocopy of a typescript of the last 8 stanzas of "Full Fathom Five" numbered 39, probably from the book The Colossus [1959-1960].
    - Photocopy of printed version of "Full Fathom Five", 1959 (Box 9, Folder 102, Item 3)
      Photocopy of printed version from Audience volume 6, pages 34-35.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "Full Fathom Five" and "The Sleepers", 1960 June (Box 9, Folder 102, Item 4)
      Photocopy of printed version from The London Magazine volume 7, number 6, pages 12-13. The poems are headed "Sylvia Plath Two Poems."
      Gift of Ruth Mortimer Lancaster, Smith College class of 1953, 06/18/1982.
    - Holograph of "Getting There", 1962 November 3; 2 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 9, Folder 103, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Getting There." The backs of the pages have pages 1 and 2 of Sylvia Plath's revised, undated review of the children's books The Wonderful Button, Little Blue and Little Yellow, Punch and Judy Carry On, The Mellops Go Flying, Achilles the Donkey, and Horton Hatches an Egg.
    - Typescript of "Getting There", 1962 November 3; 2 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 9, Folder 103, Item 2)
      Typescript of "Getting There." The back of page 1 has Sylvia Plath's summary (revised and undated) of the following children's books: The Penguins of Penguin Town by Gaby Baldner, The Creation illustrated by Reinhard Herrman.
    - Typescript of "Getting There", 1962 November 3; 2 pages (Box 9, Folder 103, Item 3)
      Corrected typescript (carbon) of "Getting There."
    - Typescript of "Getting There", undated; 2 pages (Box 9, Folder 103, Item 4)
      Revised typescript (carbon) of "Getting There."
    - Typescript of "Getting There", undated; 4 pages (Box 9, Folder 103, Item 5)
      Revised double-spaced typescript (original and carbons) of "Getting There."
    - Typescript of "Getting There", 1962 November 3-6; 6 pages (Box 9, Folder 103, Item 6)
      Revised typescript (original and carbons) of "Getting There."
    - Photocopy of galley proof of "Getting There", "Death & Co.", "The Swarm", "The Other", "Lady Lazarus", "Little Fugue", "Childless Woman", "The Jailor", "Thalidomide", and "Daddy", 1963 October 21 (Box 9, Folder 103, Item 7)
      Printed version from Encounter published as "Ten Poems."
    - Printed version of "Getting There", 1963 October (Box 9, Folder 103, Item 8)
      Printed version from Encounter volume XXI, number 3, pages 47-48.
    - Printed version of "The Ghost's Leavetaking", 1959 July-September (Box 9, Folder 104)
      Two copies of a printed version from The Sewanee Review volume 67, pages 446-48, with published title "The Departure of the Ghost." The printed version is title "Two Poems by Sylvia Plath" and includes the poem "Point Shirley."
    - Holograph of "Gigolo", 1963 January 29; 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 105, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Gigolo" with Sylvia Plath's "Berck-Plage": item 8, page 3 on the back.
    - Typescript of "Gigolo", 1963 January 29; 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 105, Item 2)
      Revised typescript of "Gigolo" with Sylvia Plath's "Death & Co.": item 9, page 2 on the back.
    - Typescript (originals and carbons) of "Gigolo", 1963 January 29; 3 pages (Box 9, Folder 105, Item 3)
    - Typescript of "Gigolo", 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 105, Item 4)
      Carbon typescript of "Gigolo" corrected with printer's annotations for The New Yorker 1970 April 24.
    - Typescript of "Go Get the Goodly Squab", undated (Box 9, Folder 106, Item 1)
      Typescript of "Go Get the Goodly Squab" annotated by Sylvia Plath. "Sold Harper's April 1953" is annotated at the top in Sylvia Plath's hand.
    - Typescript of "Go Get the Goodly Squab" (Box 9, Folder 106, Item 2)
      Typescript (carbon) of "Go Get the Goodly Squab" page numbered 31, probably from the book "Two lovers and a Beachcomber" [1956-1957].
    - Printed version of "Go Get the Goodly Squab", 1954 November (Box 9, Folder 106, Item 3)
      Printed version from Harper's volume 209, number 1254, page 47. Signed "Sylvia Plath" on the first page and annotated by Aurelia Plath on the cover and contents page.
    - Typescript of "Goatsucker", between 1959 January and June (Box 9, Folder 107, Item 1)
    - Typescript of "Goatsucker", between 1959 January and June (Box 9, Folder 107, Item 2)
      Typescript carbon of "Goatsucker", revised by Sylvia Plath.
    - Photocopies of a typescript of "Gone is the River" and letter to Hans Joachim Neupert, 1949 October 10 (Box 9, Folder 107.1)
      Typescript carbon of "Goatsucker" headed "Syliva Plath Age 16 Wellesley, Mass." Enclosed with letter to Hans Joachim Neupert, 1949 Oct 10, in which she discusses this and other enclosed poems ("The Stranger," "The Farewell," "White Phlox," and "City Streets.")
    - Typescript of "The Goring", 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 108)
      Typescript of "The Goring" numbered 57, probably from the book "The Bull of Bendylaw" [1958-1959]. "(Arts in Society)" is typed at the top of the page and "1956" is written at the bottom.
    - Photocopy of typescript of "The Great Carbuncle", undated (Box 9, Folder 109)
      Photocopy of a typescript of "The Great Carbuncle" on the reverse of "Whiteness I Remember", item 1.
      Original typescript is on the reverse of "Whiteness I Remember" (item 1).
    - Typescript of "Green Rock, Winthrop Bay", 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 110)
      Typescript of "Green Rock, Winthrop Bay" page numbered 8, probably from the book "The Bull of Bendylaw" [1958-1959].
    - Holograph of "Gulliver", undated; 1 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 9, Folder 111, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Gulliver", variant title "Gulliver in Lilliput."
    - Typescript of "Gulliver", 1962 November 3; 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 111, Item 2)
      Corrected typescript of "Gulliver."
    - Typescript of "Gulliver", 1962 November 3; 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 111, Item 3)
      Corrected typescript carbon of "Gulliver."
    - Typescript of "Gulliver", undated; 2 pages (Box 9, Folder 111, Item 4)
      Revised double-spaced typescript (original and carbon) of "Gulliver."
    - Typescript of "Gulliver", undated (Box 9, Folder 111, Item 5)
      Revised typescript carbon of "Gulliver."
    - Typescript of "Gulliver", 1962 November 3-6; 3 pages (Box 9, Folder 111, Item 6)
      Revised typescript (original and carbons) of "Gulliver."
    - Typescript of "Gulliver", probably 1962 December-1963 February; 1 pages (Box 9, Folder 111, Item 7)
    - Typescript of "The Hanging Man", 1960 June 27 (Box 10, Folder 112, Item 1)
    - Typescript of "The Hanging Man", between 1961 September and 1962 December (Box 10, Folder 112, Item 2)
    - Printed version of "Hardcastle Crags", 1958 October 11 (Box 10, Folder 113, Item 1)
      Two copies of the printed version of "Hardcastle Crags" from The New Yorker volume 34, page 40, published as "Night Walk." One copy is annotated by Sylvia Plath.
    - Printed version of "Hardcastle Crags", 1958 October 11 (Box 10, Folder 113, Item 2)
      Printed version of "Hardcastle Crags" from The New Yorker volume 34, page 40, published as "Night Walk." Annotations by Aurelia Plath on the cover.
    - Typescript of "Harlequin Love Song", 1955 January 20 (Box 10, Folder 114, Item 1)
      Typescript of "Harlequin Love Song" edited and annotated by Sylvia Plath with additional annotations by Alfred Young Fisher. "Sylvia Plath January 20 1955 for Mr. Fisher" is typed on the reverse. Not printed in Collected Poems".
    - Typescript of "Harlequin Love Song", between 1957 September and 1958 September (Box 10, Folder 114, Item 2)
      Typescript of "Harlequin Love Song" Not printed in Collected Poems".
    - Typescript of "Heavy Women", 1961 February 22 (Box 10, Folder 115, Item 1)
      Typescript of "Heavy Women" with "Poetry Chicago" and the date annotated in Sylvia Plath's hand at the top of the page.
    - Typescript of excerpts of "Heavy Women" and "Stars over the Dordogne", undated (Box 10, Folder 115, Item 2)
      Typescript carbon of excerpts from "Heavy Women" and "Stars over the Dordogne" with "POETRY, March issue, 1962" typed at the top of the page.
    - Printed version of "The Hermit at Outermost House", 1959 November 6 (Box 10, Folder 116, Item 1)
      Printed version from Times Literary Supplement 1959 November 6, page xxix with annotations by Sylvia Plath. The index also lists "Two Views of a Cadaver Room."
    - Printed version of "The Hermit at Outermost House", 1959 Spring (Box 10, Folder 116, Item 2)
      Two copies of the printed version from Audience 1959 Spring, page 36. The back of the page has "Full Fathom Five" corrected by Sylvia Plath. Also included is a photocopy of the double-page spread from Audience.
    - Photocopy of a typescript of "The Hermit at Outermost House" (Box 10, Folder 116, Item 3)
      Photocopy of a typescript of "The Hermit at Outermost House" numbered 49, probably from the book The Colossus [1959-1960].
    - Printed email from Peter K. Steinberg with typed text of "Home Thoughts from London" (Box 10, Folder 117)
      Printout of email with typed text of poem located by Peter K. Steinberg at Indiana University. Not printed in The Collected Poems.
    - Typescript of "I Am Vertical", 1961 March 28 (Box 10, Folder 118, Item 1)
      Carbon typescript of "I Am Vertical" annotated by Sylvia Plath. "Critical Quarterly" and the date are annotated at the top in Sylvia Plath's hand.
    - Photocopy of a typeset proof of "I Am Vertical" and "Private Ground", probably 1961; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 118, Item 2)
      Photocopy of a typeset proof for publication in Critical Quarterly.
      Original: Box 12, Folder 202, item 2.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "I Am Vertical", Summer 1961 (Box 10, Folder 118, Item 3)
      Photocopy of printed version in Critical Quarterly volume 3, number 2, pages 140-141.
      Original: Box 12, Folder 202, item 3.
    - Typescript of "Ice Age" (I), probably 1955 (Box 10, Folder 119, Item 1)
      Typescript of "Ice Age" annotated by Alfred Young Fisher.
    - Typescript of "Ice Age" (I), between 1957 September and 1958 September (Box 10, Folder 119, Item 2)
      Typescript of "Ice Age" with "(I)" added to the title by Sylvia Plath. Not printed in The Collected Poems.
    - Typescript of "Ice Age" (II), undated (Box 10, Folder 120)
      Typescript carbon of "Ice Age" with "(II)" added to the title by Sylvia Plath. Not printed in The Collected Poems.
    - Holograph of "In a Mossy Woodland Vale", undated (Box 10, Folder 121)
      Holograph of "In a Mossy Woodland Vale", title from first line. 5 stanzas, abcd rhyme scheme, another fragment of 4 stanzas at the top of the page. Not printed in The Collected Poems.
    - Typescript of "In Midas' Country" (Box 10, Folder 122, Item 1)
      Typescript of "In Midas' Country" with annotations by Sylvia Plath. The page is numbered 56, probably from the book "The Bull of Bendylaw" [1958-1959]. "(London Magazine)" is typed at the top of the page.
    - Typeset proof of "In Midas' Country", probably 1959; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 122, Item 2)
      Typeset proof of "In Midas' Country" for publication in The London Magazine. Also includes "The Think People."
    - Printed version of "In Midas' Country", 1959 October (Box 10, Folder 122, Item 3)
      Two copies of the printed version of "In Midas' Country" and "The Thin People" from The London Magazine volume 6, number 10, page 11. One copy is annotated by Sylvia Plath at the top: "London Magazine: October 1959", with the front cover of magazine. The other copy (removed from Sylvia Plath's scrapbook) is a clipping of just "In Midas' Country."
    - Typescript of "In Plaster", 1961 between March and August; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 123, Item 1)
      Typescript carbon of "In Plaster" annotated and corrected by Sylvia Plath with "London Mag" annotated at the top in Sylvia Plath's hand.
    - Photocopy of a typescript of "In Plaster", undated; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 123, Item 2)
      Photocopy of a typescript carbon of "In Plaster" lacking "next page."
      Original filed with "The Other"
    - Photocopy of printed version of "In Plaster", 1964 (Box 10, Folder 123, Item 3)
      Photocopy of printed version from New Poetry 1964: Critical Quarterly Poetry Supplement number 5, pages 4-5.
    - Typescript of "Insolent Storm Strikes at the Skull", probably 1955 (Box 10, Folder 124)
      Typescript of "Insolent Storm Strikes at the Skull" corrected by Sylvia Plath and annotated by Alfred Young Fisher.
    - Typescript of "Insomniac", 1961 (Box 10, Folder 125, Item 1)
      Typescript of "Insomniac" annotated by Sylvia Plath. "Cheltenham Festival Prize: 1961" typed at the top of the page.
    - Typescript of "Insomniac", 1961 May (Box 10, Folder 125, Item 2)
      Typescript carbon of "Insomniac" annotated by Sylvia Plath. "Cheltenham Festival: First Prize Guinness Book" annotated at the top in Sylvia Plath's hand.
    - Typescript of "Insomniac", between 1961 August and 1962 December (Box 10, Folder 125, Item 3)
      Revised of "Insomniac" revised by Sylvia Plath.
    - Printed version of "Insomniac", 1962 October 1-6 (Box 10, Folder 125, Item 4)
      Printed version in Handbook of the Cheltenham Festival of Literature 1 October-6 October 1962, page 71 and 73. Page headed "The Guinness Poetry Award 1961, first prize winner."
    - Typescript of "Item: Stolen, One Suitcase", probably 1955 (Box 10, Folder 126)
      Typescript of "Item: Stolen, One Suitcase." Not printed in The Collected Poems.
    - Holograph of "The Jailor", undated; 1 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 1)
      Holograph titled "The Jailer." The back of the page has page 20 of Ted Hughes' play "The Calm."
    - Holograph of "The Jailor", undated; 3 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 2)
      Revised holograph titled "The Jailer", numbered 2-4. The backs of the pages have pages 16, 18, and 19 of Ted Hughes' play "The Calm."
    - Typescript of "The Jailor", 1962 October 17; 2 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 3)
      Revised typescript titled "The Jailer." The back of the pages have pages 15 and 17 of Ted Hughes' play "The Calm."
    - Typescript of "The Jailor", 1962 October 17; 3 pages (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 4)
      Original and carbon of a revised typescript of "The Jailor."
    - Typescript of "The Jailor", undated; 4 pages (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 5)
      Original and carbons of a revised typescript of "The Jailor", double-spaced.
    - Typescript of "The Jailor", 1962 October 17; 3 pages (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 6)
      Original and carbons of a revised typescript of "The Jailor."
    - Typescript of "The Jailor", 1962 October 17; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 7)
      Original and carbons of a typescript of "The Jailor."
    - Typescript of "The Jailor", 1962 October 17; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 8)
      Original and carbons of a corrected typescript of "The Jailor", titled "The Jailer."
    - Typescript of "The Jailor", undated; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 9)
      Typescript of "The Jailor" double-spaced and revised.
    - Typescript of "The Jailor", undated; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 10)
      Typescript carbon of "The Jailor" double-spaced.
    - Galley proof of "The Jailor" and nine other poems, 1963 October 21; 8 pages (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 11)
      Galley proof from Encounter, published as "Ten Poems." Poems included are "The Jailor", "Death & Co.", "The Swarm", "The Other", "Lady Lazarus", "Little Fugue", "Childless Woman", "Getting There", "Thalidomide", and "Daddy." Also includes typed note from the editors.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "The Jailor", 1963 October (Box 10, Folder 127, Item 12)
      Photocopy of printed version from Encounter volume XXI, number 4, page 51.
    - Holograph of "Kindness", 1963 February 1; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 128, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Kindness" with a typescript description and address of two mother's helpers on the back of the page.
    - Typescript of "Kindness", 1963 February 1; 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 128, Item 2)
      Corrected typescript of "Kindness." The back of the page: TLS to Karl Miller of The New Statesman about Lord Byron's Wife and her new address, revised 1962 November 29.
    - Typescript of "Kindness", 1963 February 1; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 128, Item 3)
      Original and carbon of a typescript of "Kindness."
    - Photocopy of the printed version of "Kindness", "Edge", "Contusion", and "The Fearful", 1963 February 17 (Box 10, Folder 128, Item 4)
      Photocopy of printed version from Observer. Also includes the paragraph, "A Poet's Epitaph," by A. Alvarez.
    - Holograph of "Lady Lazarus", undated; 6 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Lady Lazarus" numbered 1-6 by Sylvia Plath. The backs of the pages have Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar second draft, chapter 3, pages 2-6; chapter 2, page 7.
    - Incomplete typescript of "Lady Lazarus", 1962 October 23; 2 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 2)
      Incomplete typescript of "Lady Lazarus" (last three stanzas missing). The backs of the pages have Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar second draft, chapter 2, pages 8-9.
    - Incomplete typescript of "Lady Lazarus", undated; 2 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 3)
      Incomplete typescript of "Lady Lazarus" (first thirteen stanzas missing). The backs of the pages have Sylvia Plath's The Bell Jar second draft, chapter 2, pages 5-6.
    - Photocopy of an incomplete typescript of "Lady Lazarus", undated; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 4)
      Photocopies of incomplete typescript of "Lady Lazarus" (last three stanzas missing). The back of page 1 has "The Munich Mannequins": item 1, page 1. The back of page 2 has "Totem": item 1, page 2.
      Originals are with "The Munich Mannequins" and "Totem."
    - Typescript of "Lady Lazarus", 1962 October 23; 9 pages (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 5)
      Original and carbon typescript of "Lady Lazarus", revised.
    - Typescript of "Lady Lazarus", undated; 8 pages (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 6)
      Original and carbon typescript of "Lady Lazarus", double-spaced and revised.
    - Typescript of "Lady Lazarus", 1962 October 29; 6 pages (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 7)
      Original and carbon typescript of "Lady Lazarus."
    - Photocopy of galley proof of "Lady Lazarus" and nine other poems, 1963 October 21 (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 8)
      Photocopy of a galley proof for Encounter. Published as "Ten Poems." Poems includes are: "Lady Lazarus," "Death & Co.," "The Swarm," "The Other," "The Jailor," "Little Fugue," "Childless Woman," "Getting There," "Thalidomide," and "Daddy."
      Original filed with "The Jailor": Box 10, Folder 127, item 11.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "Lady Lazarus", 1963 October (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 9)
      Photocopy of printed version in Encounter volume XXI, number 4, page 49.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "Lady Lazarus", 1963 October (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 10)
      Photocopy of printed version in The Review (Oxford, England), number 9, cover and pages 4-19. Cover has title "Sylvia Plath: The Last Poems." Includes nine other poems by Sylvia Plath.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "Lady Lazarus", 1965 (Box 10, Folder 129, Item 11)
      Photocopy of printed version in American Poetry 1965, Critical Quarterly Poetry supplement number 6, pages 3-5. Also includes, "The Bee Meeting."
      Original filed with "The Bee Meeting": Box 7, Folder 26, item 6
      Additional copy in the Mortimer Rare Book Collection: 825 P696cq suppl. 6
    - Typescript of "Lament", probably 1955 (Box 10, Folder 130, Item 1)
      Typescript of "Lament" with variant title "Dirge" and annotated by Alfred Young Fisher.
    - Typescript of "Lament", undated (Box 10, Folder 130, Item 2)
      Typescript of "Lament" with variant title "Lament (a villanelle)." "Sold: New Orleans Poetry Journal, July 1955" is annotated in Sylvia Plath's hand.
    - Carbon typescript of "Lament", not before 1956 June 16 (Box 10, Folder 130, Item 3)
    - Printed version of "Lament", 1955 October (Box 10, Folder 130, Item 4)
      Printed version from The New Orleans Poetry Journal volume 1, number 4, page 19. Sylvia Plath's signature is on the cove along with "page 19" in Aurelia Plath's hand.
      Gift of Aurelia S. Plath, likely 12/03/1983.
    - Typescript of "Landowners", 1 pages (Box 10, Folder 131)
      Typescript of "Landowners" numbered 7, probably from the book "The Bull of Bendylaw" [1958-1959].
    - Typescript of "Last Words", undated (Box 10, Folder 132, Item 1)
    - Typescript of "Last Words", 1961 October 21 (Box 10, Folder 132, Item 2)
      Carbon typescript of "Last Words" annotated by Sylvia Plath.
    - Typescript of "Leaving Early", 1960 September 25 (Box 10, Folder 133, Item 1)
      Corrected typescript of "Leaving Early" annotated by Sylvia Plath. "BBC, London Magazine, Harper's" is annotated at the top in Sylvia Plath's hand.
    - Photocopy of printed version of "Leaving Early", "Zoo Keeper's Wife", "You're", "Small Hours", "Parliament Hill Fields", and "Whitsun", 1961 August (Box 10, Folder 133, Item 2)
      Photocopy of printed version from The London Magazine new series, volume 1, number 5, pages 9-10. Page 5 is headed "Six Poems." Annotated by Aurelia Plath.
    - Holograph of "Lesbos", October 18, probably 1962; 5 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 10, Folder 134, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Lesbos" numbered 1-5 by Sylvia Plath. The back of the pages have holograph pages of Ted Hughes' play "The Calm", pages 10-14.
    - Typescript of "Lesbos", undated; 2 pages; Typed on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 10, Folder 134, Item 2)
      Revised typescript of "Lesbos" with pages 8-9 of Ted Hughes' play "The Calm" on the reverse.
    - Typescript of "Lesbos", 1962 October 18; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 134, Item 3)
      Carbon typescript of "Lesbos", revised.
    - Typescript of "Lesbos", 1962 October 18; 4 pages (Box 10, Folder 134, Item 4)
      Original and carbon typescript of "Lesbos", corrected.
    - Typescript of "Lesbos", 1962 October 18; 4 pages (Box 10, Folder 134, Item 5)
    - Printed version of "Lesbos" and nine other poems, 1963 October (Box 10, Folder 134, Item 6)
      Printed version from The Review (Oxford, England), number 9, cover and pages 4-19. Cover has title: "Sylvia Plath: The Last Poems." Includes nine other poems by Sylvia Plath.
    - Printed version of "Lesbos", 1966 May 12 (Box 10, Folder 134, Item 7)
      Printed version from New York Review of Books 12 May 1966, pages 4-5.
    - Holograph of "Letter in November", undated; 2 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 10, Folder 135, Item 1)
      Holograph of "Letter in November" numbered 1-2 by Sylvia Plath.
    - Holograph of "Letter in November", 1962 November 11; 1 pages; Written on pink Smith College memorandum paper. (Box 10, Folder 135, Item 2)
      Revised holograph of "Letter in November" numbered 3 by Sylvia Plath.
    - Typescript of "Letter in November", 1962 November 11; 3 pages (Box 10, Folder 135, Item 3)
      Original and carbon typescript of "Letter in November", corrected.
    - Typescript of "Letter in November", undated; 2 pages (Box 10, Folder 135, Item 4)